[{"answer": "Your what...", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " What are you talking about", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " You're not going to talk to anyone without a lawyer", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, I will not step outside", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What're we having", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Scrambled eggs surprise", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "The gun?  It's in the upstairs closet", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I know where everything is", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Except the goddamn skateboards, which are everywhere!  I'd like to kill the guy who invented those things", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Lay back, my friend!!  What's this", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "... He killed Win... he enjoyed it..", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "And I'm making mine", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "... Hard", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " But I got him!  He's in jail! Wasn't that the point...?", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It wasn't a bad bust.  He gave himself up because he knew I was gonna nab him", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "The real estate lady left, she couldn't wait anymore.  What took you", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What shit, honey", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Listen, that was my fault", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "If I had known I was going to have company, he was right next to me.  I think he heard me peeing!  I hate that, I am glad he's in jail", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hmm..", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "that place and Hindi", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "... It was like... the minute I saw her... I knew.  She looked so damn adorable in a cop's uniform... puttin' on a big, tough act..", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah.  It was", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "So it was", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No dog", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Very nice", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What about my friend", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " What's to like", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You don't like him, do you", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Tell it like it is", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You asked", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You could do better", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " It is my fault!  I'm responsible for her", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Did you hear what I said?!", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " What do you want", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I can't open it", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Stop being nuts", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I do care about you", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Not exactly", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "How about dinner tonight", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You coming in", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "We're not going to a singing lesson, she's just gonna start taking singing lessons", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "So, what are you doing tonight", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Shooting", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " What a memory", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Do you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": " That's right, you're gonna do what I say.  my friend.  I want to help you out of this", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I brought the girl.  She's outside", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I get my hostage first.  No one's turned loose until I say so", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I'm not lettin' no one go", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "You still going away", "docId": "Someone-To-Watch-Over-Me.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You don't have to, now", "qsentId": 56}]